NAWEID FAKEERMAHAMOOD

47, Lapotaire St, Fort-Adelaïde, 11403, Port-Louis, MAURITIUS · (230) 59 37 37 13 naweid@outlook.fr · linkedin.com/in/naweid/

I am an ambidextrous leader aiming for a challenging position to inspire change and innovation with technology while fullymaking use of my strengths in leadership, organization, and communication at international business level. I consider myself a hybrid practitioner, both a thinker and a doer, and being able not only to identify real opportunities at the fuzzy front end of the innovation process but also, design, develop and help implement the resulting consumer offers and business models. I have 14 years of career evolution in business management with focus on marketing strategy in various industries starting from local SMEs to Global Conglomerates including autonomous management roles like Country Branch Manager. Besides, I am a devoted philanthropist, and I am also dedicated to global CSR strategies.

SKILLS

- Marketing Strategy
- Client Services & Operations
- CSR, Global Pro Bono
- HR Strategy & Global recruitment
- Admin & Finance

- Business Development, Planning, Innovation & Partnerships
- Lecturing, Coaching & Mentoring
- Project Management
- Travel & Tourism

EDUCATION

AUGUST 2018

MASTER OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION, UNIVERSITY OF NORTHAMPTON- UNITED KINGDOM

MBA Merit-Level 7: Management, Marketing, Finance, Human Resources & Operations

JULY 2016

DIPLOME EN FRANÇAIS DES AFFAIRES B2, PARIS CHAMBERS OF COMMERCE AND INDUSTRY- FRANCE

Mention Très Bien

OCTOBER 2015

BACHELOR IN TOURISM ADMINISTRATION, AMITY INSTITUTE OF HIGHER EDUCATION- MAURITIUS

First Division; Honours & Award: Shri Baljit Shastri- India

EXPERIENCE

SINCE OCTOBER 2022 (2 Years)

COUNTRY REPRESENTATIVE AT FIGS EDUCATION & RESEAU COMPETENCES ET

DEVELOPMENT | Lyon, FRANCE for MAURITIUS & the INDIAN OCEAN

Leads the Mauritius country office for the national development of the 14 higher education institutions of the group Réseau Compétences Et Développement. Develop the national Marketing Strategy of the group and account for the P&L of my geography. Follow-up of national academic

Page 1 of 4

partners via student mobility and affiliations of our Bachelor, PGE and MBA programs. Management of the Mauritius branch for international recruitment. International communication and social networks. Key Account Partnership for both academic and corporate Delocalized & Digitalized Trainings distribution. Active member of the France-Mauritius Chamber of Commerce and Industry and liaise with the French Embassy including its branches like the French Institute and Campus France.

FEBRUARY 2019 to AUGUST 2019/ JANUARY 2020 to OCTOBER 2022 (3.5 YEARS)

OPERATIONS MANAGER, COMMERCIAL AND ADMINISTRATIVE DEPARTMENT MANAGER AT SPM LTÉE FOR GROUPE MUTER LOGER | Lyon, FRANCE/ Sodnac, MAURITIUS

Marketing Management and Business development of 7 business units of the group to achieve operational excellence. I reported to the President, General Director & Director of Sales of the group which provides all real estate and mobility-related services related to settlement throughout France and its outer territories. We worked with over 250 partners and the group is a national leader in geographic and professional mobility with more than 4,000 transfers managed per year. I recruited and managed different teams in this role and together we did an average of 40% increase in turnover. I also had a project challenge to digitalize the administration department of the real estate; relocation activity and performing the management functions of planning, organizing, directing, and controlling of the MOBILI-PASS financial grant with the French government's organisation: 'Action Logement'.

SINCE JULY 2019 (5 YEARS)

MANAGEMENT PROJECTS & CONSULTING SERVICES IN PARALLEL

Since December 2019

PROJECT MANAGER AT PYXERA GLOBAL FOR SAP & DELL TECHNOLOGIES |

Washington, D.C., U.S.A for EMEA region

Global Pro bono CSR Program Manager: Local Social Sabbatical and Virtual Pro Bono workshops. Tasks include but not limited to: Global recruitment of high caliber volunteers of various corporate backgrounds, Marketing & Prospecting social enterprises and NGOs/NPOs, Application, selection, and onboarding processes, Develop Scope of Works (SOWs), Travel and Event Management, Project coordination of 12 international consultants for 4 high impact social enterprises per social sabbatical program in their respective fields, Virtual Pro Bono workshops for 25 International NGOs/NPOs and 150 high caliber volunteers per session and, Monitoring and evaluation post programs.

Since July 2019

PART-TIME ACADEMIC AT AMITY INSTITUTE OF HIGHER EDUCATION |

Pierrefonds, MAURITIUS

Visiting Faculty of Marketing and Management. delivering lectures, supervising thesis work, conducting research, and participating in exams/ faculty/ curriculum development committee meetings. Preparation of teaching content, written and softcopy for publishing on Amizone. Setting and marking of examination papers/Assignments/MCQ and Invigilating examinations.

Since October 2020

EVALUATOR AT BARE INTERNATIONAL | Virginia, U.S.A.

Mystery customer research at the national and global level. As an evaluator for BARE International, I have a valuable part of providing game-changing insights to corporate clients. I can have an impact on how clients provide customer service

Page 2 of 4

| | | | |

| | | |

and make business decisions. I must meet ethical standards upheld when designing, implementing, and analyzing researchstrategies for the clients.

October 2019 - December 2019

MARKETING & FIELD OPERATIONS MANAGER AT SERVICE A LA FRANÇAISE |

AFRICA AND INDIAN OCEAN.

Management and development of the marketing BU of SAF training & consulting services in the African and Indian Ocean region. We were able to fill all classes to full capacity during my service. Field operations work included but not limited to assisting high calibre international trainers & consultants to deliver Master Classes and consulting project deliveries. The consultants are all awardees of the 'Meilleur Ouvrier de France' by the French Presidency for being the best workers of France among 240 jobs.

August 2019 - September 2019

GUEST SERVICES AT MSC | Venice, ITALY

Improving and assisting the guest relations management team of the MSC Opera 5* cruise ship inorder to enhance guest experience and customer satisfaction on board.

JANUARY 2016 – JANUARY 2019 (3 YEARS)

SENIOR TRAVEL AGENT- TEAM MANAGER & INTERNATIONAL COACH AT AMARIS GROUP (now MANTU) | GENEVA, SWITZERLAND/ MAURITIUS/ GLOBAL

The main goal was to build an IATA certified travel agency within a global consulting group which we did during the first year. Then opened branch offices and managed teams in 4 countries for clients in 55+ countries. Other management experiences included recruitment and coaching of staff in Switzerland, France, Mauritius, Romania, Tunisia, Vietnam, and Colombia. I acquired many skills while multitasking for example being the Bank Account Program Manager/ Finance and administration of the agency, handled international partnerships agreements, did Quality Management Systems (SERVQUAL, SERVPERF, Six Sigma, Balanced Scorecard), Marketing, Business Innovation and digitalization development, Supplier and Procurement Negotiation Quality, Design products, services, concepts, experiences, ecosystems. I also managed Global Travel & Big Event Agency Operations - Average annual growth of 60%, several side Project Management roles, Documentation of Business Processes (SOP/SLA, Contracts, Internal and external communication, Department Strategies), Strategic Planning. Hybrid tasks: Office management & Real estate/ Health and Safety Committee

JUNE 2014 – JANUARY 2016 (1+ YEAR)

MANAGEMENT TRAINEESHIP

December 2014 – January 2016

TRAVEL AGENCY MANAGEMENT AT ROGERS AVIATION | Port-Louis, MAURITIUS

The one+ year internship gave me hands on experience on documentation of Business Processes: SOP/SLA/Contracts, Partnership Agreements, Quality Management System and audit, Communication, Marketing & Branding, Administrative management, Travel & Tour Management, Project Management: Customer Portfolios and Profiles Mauritius and Mozambique, Statistics and Reporting, Catalogue of Services and Presentations. Tools: GDS' Amadeus, Sabre, Navision, MS Office, Airline, and other supplier negotiations. Sales techniques of booking flights, Trains, Hotels, Road Transfers, Car Rentals, Cruises, Tours & Activities including Group travel management.

June 2014 – August 2014

FOOD AND BEVERAGE MANAGEMENT AT HENNESSY PARK HOTEL (4*) | Cyber City, MAURITIUS Banqueting and Event Management, Gastronomy and Sushi Restaurant Service, Room Service, Bar.

DECEMBER 2010 – DECEMBER 2014 (3+ YEARS)

SMALL AND MEDIUM ENTERPRISES (SME) EXPERIENCE,

September 2011 – December 2014

ASSISTANT MANAGING DIRECTOR AT LEILA DÉLICES | Port-Louis, MAURITIUS

As the right hand of the business owner, we managed the business together from Product Design, Customer Service, Sales and Marketing, Admin & Finance to Human Resources.

December 2010 – September 2011

MARKETING AND ADMIN OFFICER AT ABIB METAL WORKSHOP | Port-Louis, MAURITIUS

Marketing, Admin & Finance, Customer Service, Human Resources

LANGUAGES

NATIVE FLUENCY | English, French and Mauritian Creole

NOVICE CONVERSATIONAL Italian, Spanish, Portuguese, Arabic and Turkish

ACTIVITIES

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE AND LEADERSHIP

- August 2012 August 2014: President; Vice- President; Event Manager at Amity Mauritius Student Council
- January 2013 December 2018: Event Coordinator at Young Students' Association and project initiator
- 12th March 2012 Theatre Actor for the Ministry of Art & Culture for the 40th IndependenceAnniversary Ceremony
- 2008- 2011 Executive and Active member of London College Human Rights Club and AmnestyInternational
- 2006- 2009 First Aider of St John Ambulance

OTHER EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS

2017 (STCW) FOR SEAFARERS – MMTA | 2010 DELF B2 (CIEP- Sévres)- France | 2015: Sabre Travel Network Training |2013: Amity University: Bloom's Taxonomy, Soft Skills, and Enhancing Employability Master Classes |2010, 2009, 2007 - Cambridge A, AS, O levels science side, MUN delegate |2001 Certificat de Mérite au Concours de Langue Française.

INTERESTS, PASSIONS & HOBBIES

Volunteering and community involvement, New Technology, AI, public speaking, teaching, learning languages, Event Management, Writing, Fashion design, Creative Arts, Music, Backpack Travelling, Ocean lover and nature exploration.

REFERENCES

AVAILABLE ON REQUEST